Finding aid for the Sam Manners papers, 1966-1988 LSC.2259
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Television Projects, 1956-1981; (Boxes 1-10)
  - Route 66: Burning for Burning - script, 1961 Oct 30 (Box 4)
  - Route 66: The Cage Around Maria - script, 1963 Feb 18 (Box 5)
  - Route 66: A Cage in Search of a Bird - final draft screenplay, 1963 Jun 3 (Box 5)
  - Route 66: Child of a Night - script, 1963 Dec 5 (Box 5)
  - Route 66: City of Wheels - script, 1962 Jan 12 (Box 4)
  - Route 66: Come Out, Come Out Wherever You Are! - revised final draft screenplay, 1963 Aug 23 (Box 5)
  - Route 66: Cries of Persons Close to One - script, 1963 Dec 27 (Box 6)
    In bound volume labeled Route 66 Series VI, Volume XVII, 1963-1964.
  - Route 66: Every Father's Daughter - script, 1962 Oct 4 (Box 5)
    In bound volume labeled Route 66 Series III, Volume XII, 1962-1963.
  - Route 66: Ever Ride the Waves in Oklahoma? - first draft screenplay, 1962 Jun 8 (Box 5)
  - Route 66: A Feat of Strength - script, no date (Box 4)
  - Route 66: Fifty Miles From Home - script, 1963 Feb 28 (Box 5)
  - Route 66: Follow the White Dove with the Broken Wing - script, 1964 Jan 30 (Box 6)
  - Route 66: From an Enchantress Fleeing - script, no date (Box 4)
  - Route 66: A Gift for a Warrior - revised first draft screenplay, 1962 May 21 (Box 5)
  - Route 66: Give the Old Cat a Tender Mouse - script, 1962 Nov 27 (Box 5)
  - Route 66: Go Read the River - script, 1962 Feb 22 (Box 4)
  - Route 66: Hey, Moth, Come Eat the Flame - script, 1962 Oct 30 (Box 5)
  - Route 66: How Much a Pound is Albatross? - script, 1962 Jan 19 (Box 4)
  - Route 66: I Wouldn't Start From Here - script, 1963 Oct 1 (Box 5)
  - Route 66: I'm Here to Kill a King - script, 1963 Oct 21 (Box 5)
  - Route 66: In the Closing of a Trunk - script, 1963 Feb 4 (Box 5)
  - Route 66: Is It True There are Poxies at the Bottom of Landfair Lake? - script, 1963 Dec 9 (Box 5)
  - Route 66: Journey to Nineveh - polished final draft screenplay, 1962 Jun 12 (Box 5)
  - Route 66: Kiss the Maiden All Forlorn - revised script, 1962 Mar 12 (Box 4)
  - Route 66: Kiss the Monster -- Make Him Sleep - final draft screenplay, 1963 Jul 25 (Box 5)
  - Route 66: Like This It Means Father.. Like This -- Bitter... Like This -- Tiger... - final draft screenplay, 1963 Nov 25 (Box 6)
  - Route 66: Lizard's Leg and Owlet's Wing - script, 1962 Sep 17 (Box 5)
  - Route 66: A Long Piece of Mischief - script, 1961 Dec 20 (Box 4)
  - Route 66: A Long Way Home From St. Louie - script, 1963 Nov 13 (Box 5)
  - Route 66: Love is a Skinny Kid - script, no date (Box 4)
  - Route 66: And Make Thunder His Tribute - final draft screenplay, 1963 Jul 17 (Box 5)
  - Route 66: Man Out of Time - final draft screenplay, 1962 Aug 1 (Box 5)
  - Route 66: The Most Beautiful Garbage Can in the World - script, 1962 Mar 7 (Box 4)
  - Route 66: The Mud Nest - script, 1961 Oct 17 (Box 4)
  - Route 66: Once to Every Man - revised screenplay, 1961 Sep 11 (Box 4)
  - Route 66: One Tiger to a Hill - final draft screenplay, 1962 Jul 16 (Box 5)
  - Route 66: Only By Cunning Glimpses - script, 1962 Oct 18 (Box 5)
  - Route 66: Poor Little Kangaroo Rat, 1962 Jun 19 (Box 5)
  - Route 66: Same Picture, Different Frame - final draft screenplay, 1963 Jul 29 (Box 5)
  - Route 66: Shoulder the Sky, My Lad - script, 1962 Feb 14 (Box 4)
  - Route 66: Soda Pop and Paper Flags - script, 1963 Apr 12 (Box 5)
  - Route 66: Some of the People, Some of the Time - 1961 Nov 7 (Box 4)
  - Route 66: Somehow It Gets to Be Tomorrow - script, 1963 Jan 29 (Box 5)
  - Route 66: The Stone Guest - final draft screenplay, 1963 Jun 15 (Box 5)
  - Route 66: Suppose I Said I Was the Queen of Spain - script, 1963 Jan 16 (Box 5)
  - "Route 66" The Television Series 1960-1964 - book by James Rosin, ca. 2007 (Box 11)
  - Route 66: There I Am - There I Always Am - script, no date (Box 4)
  - Route 66: The Thin White Line - script, 1961 Nov 20 (Box 4)
  - Route 66: This is Going to Hurt Me More Than it Hurts You - script, 1964 Jan 22 (Box 6)
  - Route 66: To Bury Strangers In - script, no date (Box 4)
  - Route 66: You Never Had It So Good - script, 1962 Jan 30 (Box 4)
  - Route 66: Voice at the End of the Line - final draft screenplay, 1962 Jul 20 (Box 5)
  - Route 66: Welcome to the Wedding - script, 1962 Oct 11 (Box 5)
  - Route 66: Where are the Sounds of Celli Brahms? - final draft screenplay, 1963 Jul 1 (Box 5)
  - Route 66: Where is Chick Lorimer, Where Has She Gone? - script, 1962 Nov 12 (Box 5)
  - Route 66: Where There's a Will, There's a Way - script, 1964 Feb 14 (Box 6)
  - Route 66: Where There's a Will, There's a Way Part Two - script, 1964 Feb 18 (Box 6)
  - Route 66: Who In His Right Mind Needs a Nice Girl - script, 1964 Jan 6 (Box 6)
  - Route 66: You Can't Pick Cotton in Tahiti - script, 1962 Dec 10 (Box 5)
  - The Second Marion Turner the Third is a Four Flusher - script written by Sam Manners, 1970 Jul 4 (Box 8)
  - Something Evil - second draft script, 1971 Sep 28 (Box 7)
  - Tarzan and the Treasure of Tucumai, undated (Box 10)
  - The Venturers: ... And Two If By Sea - final draft script, 1959 Dec 18 (Box 8)
  - The Wild Wild West: The Night of the Bleak Island - final draft script, 1968 Dec 3 (Box 6)
    In bound volume labeled Wild Wild West Series IV, Volume V, 1967-1968.
  - The Wild Wild West: The Night of the Cossacks - final draft script, 1969 Jan 13 (Box 6)
  - The Wild Wild West: The Night of the Death Masks - first draft script, 1967 Nov 17 (Box 6)
    In bound volume labeled Wild Wild West Series IV, Volume III, 1967-1968.
  - The Wild Wild West: The Night of the Diva - final draft script, 1968 Dec 10 (Box 6)
  - The Wild Wild West: The Night of Fire and Brimstone - second draft script, 1968 Aug 1 (Box 6)
  - The Wild Wild West: The Night of the Janus - final draft script, 1968 Oct 15 (Box 6)
  - The Wild Wild West: The Night of Miguelito's Revenge - final draft script, 1968 Sep 6 (Box 6)
  - The Wild Wild West: The Night of the Pelican - second draft script, 1968 Sep 16 (Box 6)
  - The Wild Wild West: The Night of the Plague - final draft script, 1968 Dec 30 (Box 6)
  - The Wild Wild West: The Night of the Sabatini Death - revised final draft script, 1968 Oct 23 (Box 6)
    In bound volume labeled Wild Wild West Series IV, Volume IV, 1967-1968.
  - The Wild Wild West: The Night of the Tycoons - final draft script, 1968 Nov 21 (Box 6)
  - The Wild Wild West: The Night of the Winged Terror - final draft script, 1968 Nov 1 (Box 6)
  - The Wild Wild West: The Night of the Winged Terror Part II - final draft script, 1968 Nov 1 (Box 6)
- Motion Picture Projects, 1966-1975; (Boxes 10 - 11)
  This series consists of bound scripts from a variety of motion picture projects in which Manners was involved. Included are scripts documenting Cleopatra Jones, The Deadly Trackers, and Valdez is Coming, among others. Additionally, there is a small number of photographs from the film The Deadly Trackers. The series is arranged alphabetically by project title.
  - Billy the Kid Versus Dracula! - script, ca. 1966 (Box 11)
  - Black Gunn - script, ca. 1972 (Box 10)
  - Cleopatra Jones - revised draft script, 1972 Dec 8 (Box 10)
  - The Deadly Trackers- final draft script, 1973 April 30 (Box 10)
  - [The Deadly Trackers] photographs, undated (Box 11)
    Sam Manners, Richard Harris, and other unidentified persons.
  - Heaven with a Gun - script, 1968 Apr 3 (Box 10)
  - Jesse James Meets Frankenstein's Daughter - script, ca. 1966 (Box 10)
  - The Last Hard Man - final script, 1975 Sep 26 (Box 11)
  - Valdez is Coming - revised final script, 1969 Sep 1 (Box 10)
  - Will Grow the Seeds by - script written by Sam Manners, 1972 Jan 13 (Box 8)
- Photographs, undated; (Box 11)
  The series consists of personal photographs and photographs not identified with known television or film projects. Includes images of Joan Crawford, James Earl Jones, Rod Taylor, Sam Manners and other unidentified individuals. Additionally included are autographed photographs of Bernie Casey, Dean Martin, Joe Namath, and Paul Richards. There is no specific arrangement to the series. Additional photographs may be found in the Television Projects series and the Motion Picture Projects series.
  - Personal photographs (5 items), undated (Box 11)
    Mostly young Sam Manners.
  - Manners and others (mostly unidentified) (20 items), undated (Box 11)
    With Sam Manners, Joan Crawford, James Earl Jones, Rod Taylor, and other unidentified persons.
  - Signed photographs (5 items), undated (Box 11)
    Photographs signed to either Joyce or Sam [Manners]. Head shots of Bernie Casey, Dean Martin, Joe Namath, and Paul Richards. One photograph with a signature that is undecipherable.